[音樂]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德(Douglas Crockford)：所以，我們有幾次非常接近。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So, we've gotten very close a couple of times.
它與推動有關。
It is concerned with Push.
它涉及一個函式，該函式將返回以下內容。
It is concerned with a function that will return this.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器2：那麼，我退回這個或
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So, I return this or
使用這個，它指的是。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：陣列或
uses this, it's referring to. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: The array or
它是指向量嗎？&gt；&gt；揚聲器2：陣列。
is it referring to vector? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The array.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：所以[INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So [INAUDIBLE]
通過[INAUDIBLE]的長度。
through the length of [INAUDIBLE].
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：如果你把一個函式推到上面，如果你在上面追加一個函式。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: If you push a function onto If you append a function onto this.
你可以這麼說。
You call that.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：它沒有通過嗎？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Is it not passing
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的，是的。
a function to one of these? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yes, it does.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：如果該功能
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: If that function
把這個包含在它裡面，你叫那個函式，這個的範圍是什麼？
includes this inside of it and you call that function what the scope of this?
他們會是的。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德(Douglas Crockford)：這將取決於
They would be. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It will depend on
函式的呼叫方式位呼叫函式有四種不同的方式
how the function is called bit there are four different ways to call a function and
這會發生什麼取決於它是哪種形式的呼叫。
what happens to this depends on which form of call it is.
&gt；&gt；演講者3：我們希望如此。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We want it to be.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：你希望它是
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: You want it to be
方法形式？&gt；&gt；演講者3：什麼是
the method form? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: What's
那看起來像？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：看起來
that look like? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It looks
類似於方法呼叫。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：好的。
like a method invocation. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器4：該函式可以
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: The function could
將此分配給全域性。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德(Douglas Crockford)：有可能。
assign this to a global. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It could.
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的，不是這樣的
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right, that's not so
事實上，這是一種可能的利用這一點的方式。
and in fact that is a possible way of exploiting this.
但這不是這次襲擊的關鍵。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：好的，那麼
But it's not key to the attack. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay, so
我進去了，我推到了控制檯記錄此資訊的函式的末尾
I passed in, I pushed on to the end of the function which console logs this
零，它在傳送，它在得到，它在把第一個
zero and it's sending, it's getting, it’s putting the first
將陣列中的接頭插入控制檯。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：對，
joint in the array into the console. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right,
但是他們只需呼叫Push就可以獲得陣列的第一個元素。
but they can get the first element of the array simply by calling push.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：我們想囤積，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We want to hoard,
對吧？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不一定
right? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Not necessarily
陣列的全部內容，但陣列物件本身除外。
the whole contents of the array but the array object itself.
這就是我們想要保護的東西。
That's the thing that we're trying to protect.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：對，所以我傳入一個，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Right, so I pass in a,
好的，知道了。&gt；&gt；揚聲器4：您能打個電話嗎？
okay, got it. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Can you call
這個。這個。陣列？
this.this.array?
從您傳入並存儲的函式中，我認為這不是
From a function that you pass in and you're storing I don't think that's
在整個建築中穿梭。
poking around the construct right past it all.
很抱歉，教練，我剛想到這一點。道格拉斯·克羅克福德：那不是
I'm sorry but it just struck instructor. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: That's not
來幫你。
to help you.
這本身就是。
This by itself.
如果您正確地完成了&>；&>演講者5：那麼，
If you get it done correctly as &gt;&gt; Speaker 5: So,
我沒有正確的繫結，但是我傳入了一個函式，該函式返回
I don't have this bound correctly, but I passed in a function that returns
控制檯記錄此繫結，即通過獲取一個變數，然後呼叫該變數。
a console log this bound that via get to a variable and then call the variable.
即返回視窗物件，使其走上正確的軌道，或者
That's returning the window object getting on the right track or
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不，不是。
not but &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No, it's not.
無需呼叫Window物件即可訪問該物件[CROSSTALK]
You can get to the window object without calling it [CROSSTALK]
[笑]&gt；&gt；演講者5：謝謝，
[LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Speaker 5: Thanks,
道格拉斯。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：我所做的就是推動
Douglas. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: All I do is push
其上的函式返回以下內容。
a function on it returns this.
所以
And so
現在&&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：因為我
now- &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Because I
需要知道有多少個專案，先生，現在我要在這裡得到這個函式，我想我
need to know how many items sir, now I'm gonna get this function here I guess I
我需要知道上面有多少件物品。
need to know how many items are on it.
所以現在我必須實際選擇商店，
So like, so now I have to actually choose store,
看起來像是。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：對。
looks like. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：那麼，我將儲存在
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So, I'm gonna store at
一個位置，比方說返回這個的五個函式。
a position, say five Function that returns this.
現在我要做的就是找五對
Now is all I have to call is get five pairings and
結果就是陣列。道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不，不是
the result of that's gonna be the array. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No, it's not but
你離我們越來越近了。
you're getting closer.
您確實想儲存您的函式&gt；&gt；演講者3：好的。
You do want to store your function &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：那麼，你
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So, the thing you
我還沒有了解到i。&gt；&gt；的價值。演講者3：[笑]
haven't got yet is the value of i. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: [LAUGH]
&gt；&gt；演講者3：我們從來沒有得到i的價值。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We never got the value of i.
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah,
進行這種攻擊的原因是i有一個特定值
there is a specific value of i that makes this attack
工作。
work.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器5：未定義？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：沒有。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: Undefined? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Nope.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：1？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: One?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德(Douglas Crockford)：[笑]不，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: [LAUGH] No,
如果你說負一會發生什麼。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：我不知道。
what will happen if you say negative one. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I have no idea.
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：嗯，這需要
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Well, it'll take
托架。
the brackets.
好的，括號裡會寫著Take That Number試著把它連結到你得到的一個字串上
Right, the brackets will say take that number try to link it to a string you get
字串破折號1，然後它將儲存一個數組點破折號1。
the string dash one and then it will store a array dot dash one.
這就是它要去的地方。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：JavaScript
That's where it goes. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: JavaScript
如果您設定了一個非常高的數字，則物件不會填充，
objects don't fill in if you set a really high number,
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：沒有。
do they? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Nope.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：因為他們不是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Cuz they're not
真正的陣列。道格拉斯·克羅克福德：他們是
really arrays. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: They're
實際上是半個陣列。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：是的。
really half arrays. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：我們必須做到最大限度嗎
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Do we have to do the max
數。
number.
那個號碼。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：沒有。
That number. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：您不是在試圖儲存
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: You're not trying to store
它現在的長度加一。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：沒有。
it current length plus one. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：你不知道長度。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You don't know the length.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：否，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: No,
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：你說得對&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：就是這條路。
you're right &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: This is the way.
&gt；&gt；議長6：那麼，我是我們想要通過的人嗎？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: So, is I we want to pass and
這指的是反應。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：對不起。
this to refer to the reaction. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I'm sorry.
&gt；&gt；演講者6：我是我們想要通過的人嗎？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Is I we want to pass and
這裡指的是狂喜。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不，
this to refer to the Rapture. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No,
您希望在房屋的功能中引用此內容。
you want the reference to this to be in the function of the house.
&gt；&gt；演講者3：我不知道，在我看來
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I don't know it seems to me
你可以，但首先你要知道這一點
that you could, but first of all you have to know that this
向量可能是你正在處理的一個數組，
vector perhaps that it's an array that you're dealing with,
我想我會認為
I would think
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：對。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：如果
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: If
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：我們會假設
you- &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We'll assume that
專制是原始碼[CROSSTALK]
the autocracy is the source code [CROSSTALK]
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：您說的是任意值，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You said an arbitrary value,
那麼你就是在抹掉那個任意值，所以
then you're obliterating that arbitrary value, so
我們就隨機選一個數字5吧。
let's just choose a random number five.
首先，你得拿到5分。
First, you've gotta get five.
所以，現在你已經明白了。
So, now you've got that.
現在，您可以將此函式設定為5，該函式返回整個
Now, you can set five to this function that returns the whole
陣列。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：對。
array. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：然後，如果您需要修復
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And then, if you need to fix
該陣列中有五個
five in that array
和你第一次得到的女人在一起。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：對。
with the woman you got the first time. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right.
&gt；&gt；議長3：現在你得到了正確的答案
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And now you've got the right
一個，但你沒有。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不是因為
one but you don't don't. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Not because
才能使這種約束髮生。
in order for the binding of this to happen.
在此上下文中，您必須將其作為方法呼叫。
You have to call it as a method in this context.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：是的，我只是在玩
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah, I'm just playing in
這裡的控制檯視窗。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：好的，
the console window here. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay,
嗯。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：我記不清了，
yeah. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I'm not sure I remember,
顯然，你所做的事情。
obviously, things that you do.
就像我在這裡放了一份新選單一樣。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：對。
Act like I put a new menu here. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：所以，有一個特定的價值
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: So, there's a specific value
你是否需要儲存這個函式。
of i ever you need to store this function.
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的。&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：好的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yes. &gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Okay.
想要得到
Trying to get
也許？
the maybe?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：沒有。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：那麼，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Nope. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So,
你被難住了嗎？&gt；&gt；發言人7：不是沒有定義，他說。
are you stumped? &gt;&gt; Speaker 7: It's not undefined he said.
所以[笑]&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：這不是不確定的。
So [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It's not undefined.
沒有嗎？
No?
&gt；&gt；揚聲器7：[laugh]&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：空。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Null.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德(Douglas Crockford)：不是這樣的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: it's not.
它不是空的，它不是1。&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：您能遞給我一個嗎？
Its not null its not one. &gt;&gt; Speaker 6: Could you pass it one of
該陣列的功能類似於數學？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：你可以，
the array functions like math? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: You can,
但那幫不了你。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：零？
but that's not going to help you. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Zero?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不是零。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It's not zero.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：怎麼會有一些神奇的數字，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: How could some magic number,
嘿，來吧。&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：[笑]是42嗎？
hey come on. &gt;&gt; Speaker 6: [LAUGH] Is it 42?
是三個嗎？&gt；&gt；演講者7：是factor.type，還是
Is it three? &gt;&gt; Speaker 7: Is it factor.prototype, or
差不多吧？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不是。
something like that? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Nope.
&gt；&gt；演講者7：這不是一些
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: It's not some
奇怪的魔術數字。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德(Douglas Crockford)：這不是奇怪的
weird magic number. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It's not a weird
魔術數字。&gt；&gt；揚聲器7：好的。
magic number. &gt;&gt; Speaker 7: Okay.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：42。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: 42.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器7：太高了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: That's high.
這真是太奇怪了。道格拉斯·克羅克福德：事實上，
That is very strange. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: In fact,
它甚至不是一個數字。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：這不是一個數字嗎？
it's not even a number. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Is it not a number?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德(Douglas Crockford)：不是
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It is not not
一個數字。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：[笑]這是一個數字！
a number. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: [LAUGH] It's a number!
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德(Douglas Crockford)：[笑]
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: [LAUGH]
不是數字
Not a number
是一個數字。&gt；&gt；揚聲器7：那麼，
is a number. &gt;&gt; Speaker 7: So,
這不是一個數字，就像NaN？&gt；&gt；演講者3：不，它不是NaN。
it is not a number, like NAN? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No it's not NAN.
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不，這是
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No, it's
不是南。&gt；&gt；演講者3：功能怎麼樣？
not NAN. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: How about function?
&gt；&gt；演講者7：我說我們只要
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: I say we just go for
你們覺得怎麼樣？&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：你們要
it, what do you guys think? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Are you gonna
讓他告訴我們？&&gt；&gt；演講者7：你
make him tell us? &gt;&gt; Speaker 7: You
男人們肯定有非常嚴重的黑客攻擊&>&>演講者3：我不能放棄
guys must have very serious hacking &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I can not give up
答案是，我們可以整天呆在這裡有人在谷歌上搜索它，
the answer, we could be here all day Somebody Google it,
這樣我們就可以假裝我們拿到了。&gt；&gt；揚聲器7：之後
so we can pretend like we got it. &gt;&gt; Speaker 7: After
溢位來了。&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：[笑]是評估
overflow. &gt;&gt; Speaker 6: [LAUGH] is eval
在這裡的任何地方都可以玩。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不，
play anywhere in this. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: No,
我們不是在用艾娃。
we're not using eval.
這是個很好的問題。
That's a really good question.
伊瓦爾是個麻煩纏身的人，但那是，
Eval is full of trouble but that's,
我們不關心這裡的艾娃。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：是字串嗎？
we're not concerned about eval here. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It is a string?
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：它是一個字串。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It is a string.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：for
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: For
每一個。
each.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：沒有。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Nope.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：[笑]空字串。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 6: [LAUGH] The empty string.
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：所以，這不是
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So, it's not
空字串。&gt；&gt；揚聲器6：這根弦？
the empty string. &gt;&gt; Speaker 6: The string this?
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It is
不是兩根繩子。&gt；&gt；揚聲器4：[笑]不是弦的問題
not two string. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: [LAUGH] It is not the string
這個？&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不是弦的問題
this? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It is not the string
這。&gt；&gt；揚聲器7：這是一把鑰匙，
this. &gt;&gt; Speaker 7: This is a key,
這是。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：是嗎
this is. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Is it
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：不是
every? &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It is not
每個。&gt；&gt；揚聲器7：不是字串或
every. &gt;&gt; Speaker 7: Not the string or
陣列。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：還有另一個功能
array. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: There's another function
您可以呼叫一個數組。道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的。
that you can call an array. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yes.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：好的，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Well, okay,
道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的，
is it &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yes,
它就是其中之一。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：好的。
it is one of those. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Okay.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器7：所以，它必須在陣列中
&gt;&gt; Speaker 7: So, it has to be in array
方法，它是推送的。道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的。
method, it's push. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: It is
推。&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：那麼，
push. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So,
你定好了。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：是的，那麼。
you set. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right, so.
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：您儲存推送。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You store push.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我們用來儲存推送
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We store push with
可以訪問它的函式。
a function that has access to this.
那麼，那麼問題是，如何讓該函式被呼叫呢？
So, then the question is, how do you get that function to get called?
&gt；&gt；揚聲器3：你說了算。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You call a pen.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克羅克福德：你說了算。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: You call a pen.
女士們先生們。&gt；&gt；[掌聲]
Ladies and gentlemen. &gt;&gt; [APPLAUSE]